[
    {
        "question" : "Designer of C++ programming language is",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Charles Babbage",
            "Dennis Ritchie",
            "Brian Kernighan",
            "Bjarne Stroustrup"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Bjarne Stroustrup"
    },
	{
        "question" : "The programs machine instructions are store in __ memory segment.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Data",
            "Stack",
            "Heap",
            "Code"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Code"
    },
	{
        "question" : "With respective to streams >> (operator) is called as",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Insertion operator",
            "Extraction operator",
            "Right shift operator",
            "Left shift operator"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Extraction operator"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which operator is required to be overloaded as member function only?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "_",
            "--",
            "++",
            "="
        ],        
        "answer" : "="
    },
	{
        "question" : "Runtime polymorphism is done using",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Function overloading",
            "Virtual classes",
            "Virtual functions",
            "Friend function"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Virtual functions"
    },
	{
        "question" : "What happens when a class with parameterized constructors and having no default constructor is used in a program and we create an object that needs a zero-argument constructor?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Compile-time error",
            "Preprocessing error",
            "Runtime error",
            "Runtime exception"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Compile-time error"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Can a class have virtual destructor?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Yes"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following statements is incorrect?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Friend keyword can be used in the class to allow access to another class.",
            "Friend keyword can be used for a function in the public section of a class.",
            "Friend keyword can be used for a function in the private section of a class.",
            "Friend keyword can be used on main()."
        ],        
        "answer" : "Friend keyword can be used on main()."
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following can access private data members or member functions of a class?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Any function in the program",
            "All global functions in the program",
            "Any member function of that class",
            "Only public member functions of that class"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Any member function of that class"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following type of data member can be shared by all instances of its class?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Public",
            "Inherited",
            "Static",
            "Friend"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Static"
    }   
]